<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dexter&#39;s Personal Site</title>
    <link>https://dextervolkman.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dexter&#39;s Personal Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:43:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dextervolkman.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Install</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/arch_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/arch_install/</guid>
      <description>Intro I recently finished creating a home backup server so that I can start taking backups of my laptop automatically. It is a project that lays some groundwork for future systems I would like to implement. The server is working now and I want to take some time to document the pieces that I needed to get the basic operating system installed. This is meant to be a more generic server installation with a few items that were specific to the dv-storage server I was working on getting ready at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mpd not working? Try starting with --user</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/mpd_not_working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 21:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/mpd_not_working/</guid>
      <description>This is an issue that has happened more than once now. I&amp;rsquo;ll restart my computer and ncmpcpp will not be able to locate the mpd database. If this happens here is what you should try.
Check if an mpd server is running with:
systemctl status mpd If the service is active, stop it with:
systemctl stop mpd.socket systemctl stop mpd Once it is stopped you can start it with the current user:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve been learning</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 20:34:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/links/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to figure out a good way to compile a list of all the content I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading/watching. I usually find something interesting every day but outside of my browser history I don&amp;rsquo;t have a good way to look back at the all the interesting links I&amp;rsquo;ve found. I would like to have a nicely organized way to keep track of this but until I come up with a design I like, I thought I could at least start to keep track of the links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tar Backup and Restore</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/tar-backup-and-restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 15:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/tar-backup-and-restore/</guid>
      <description>Preamble In my quest to learn and become more proficient with computers, I will often have some kind of ongoing personal project that I will work on in my spare time. Over the past few weeks the project that has taken up my evenings has been building a Linux From Scratch system. The goal is to build a working linux system by downloading and compiling everything manually from the source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Bootable USB with dd</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/bootable-usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 17:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/bootable-usb/</guid>
      <description>This is something I have had to lookup on more than one occasion and would like my own reference so that I don&amp;rsquo;t have to look it up anymore.
First locate the name of the device using:
lsblk and/or
sudo fdisk -l In my case it is sdb. Make sure the device is not mounted.
umount /dev/sdb* Next we need to format the drive so that it is empty. This can be done by initializing a new file system on the disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Worth Sharing #1</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/readings-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 10:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/readings-1/</guid>
      <description>Since I don&amp;rsquo;t have any content for this site yet and I would like to get some practice putting articles together, I have an idea for a series I could do. I use an RSS reader called tmux to collect articles from a variety of different places that I find interesting. Every day I look through this list and pick out a handful of headlines that look interesting. My idea is to share these articles along with a brief explanation for why I enjoyed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interests</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 20:35:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/interests/</guid>
      <description>Links I have an RSS feed that gives me a steady supply of reading material. When I find something I find really interesting or useful I add the link to a growing list. This list can be found at https://dextervolkman.com/links
Computers I&amp;rsquo;m entirely self-taught and have been learning about Linux and computers since college. It began as just a hobby but now that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen how much there is to learn, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could stop seeking knowledge if I tried ¯\(ツ)/¯</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 22:42:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Dexter Volkman. Online I mostly go by dexmexter. Here is a little about me for those interested.
Professional I am currently employed at Stratum Systems as an IT support technician persuading computers, networks, and people to work together productively. Most days I feel like the printers are the worst behaved obstacle to cooperation.
CV link coming soon&amp;hellip;
Internet Locations  https://dextervolkman.com LBRY.tv GitHub Email  Personal Interests More detailed list of the following can be found on the Interests page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 21:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dextervolkman.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is the first post! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure yet what I&amp;rsquo;m going to do with this space but my first instinct is to start using it as a place to write some tutorials so that I can remind my future self of all the little tips and tricks I&amp;rsquo;ve learned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>